Enter the clothing file and the top file
First check if the UV on the front of the top is normal
Then check the UV on the back of the top
First, you need to smooth out the grid of the panels to make them more evenly distributed
So if the grid is uneven in MD, you don't have to worry
If you want to adjust the edge points, you need to adjust the points on two panels at the same time
After loosening the grid, we can transfer the UV of the high-mood panels to the panels of the top
In the grid transfer attribute, we need to transfer the UV of the current panel according to the world coordinate
After the top panel has the same UV information as the clothing, we can transfer the top position according to the UV
After the top panel has the same UV information, we can transfer the UV of the current panel according to the world coordinate
Where to manually repair and transfer errors
After the top panel has the same UV information as the UV of the current panel, we can transfer the UV of the current panel according to the world coordinate
Divide the clothing into jackets, backpacks and pants
Then select the edge points and align the points
There you go for the second result
Thanks for your watching
Thank you.
For adding details and transmitting high-level details for low-model,
You
I can see the screen that I can't see when I delete it.
I will delete the invisible version.
This is the one I am going to delete.
I can't see the screen that I can't see when I delete it.
Thank you.